[Music]
Welcome to the busy central launch
edition for 2025 release wave 2. My name
is Alexander Totovich and I will show
you how you can create multiple fixed
assets.
This functionality
uh is part of our de localization
strategy because previously this feature
was part of Italian localization and now
this is available to all databases and
no localization globally. About business
values I think this is more and clear
that this is really important so you can
automate asset creation never mind how
many of them. So this is pretty often
scenario that you will purchase 10 20 30
100 the same assets. So it will automate
a lot reduce manual effort because just
imagine you need to create invoice with
the 20 absolutely the same lines. So it
will definitely reduce and forth and
improve accuracy and of course it will
handle official bulk handling for bulk
asset purchase. So let's go directly
into demo. Imagine you want to purchase
25 smartphones.
So all of them are expensive. So they
are fixed assets. What do you need to
do? You need to create new fixed assets
for the first one. And what does it
mean? You need to enter all information
for the first fixed assets. What is the
name? Uh uh category code uh and all
other information about depreciations.
So as a regular fixed assets once when
you create fixed assaets what you need
to do you need to switch to purchase
document in this case I will use
purchase order and create new one.
Okay we have already created uh header
this is just standard purchase order no
difference only what is different in
types we will use uh fixets and once
when we choose fixet yes we will use fix
set we just created. So this is a fix
set number 100 smartphone and I will
enter 25 pieces as a quantity. But now
if you click post nothing will happen.
So it will be as previously what you
need to do you need to personalize your
page. So you need to add additional
field. So just go there personalize it
will be just for once. And what you need
to do you need to add new uh field. This
is number of fixed assets cards. Add
this field into lines and after that
when you finish it will be there. So
what do you need to do? The same number
you had the quantity you need to enter
into number of fixet cards and if
everything is a good we already entered
25 here. Now you can just post document
and that's it.
nothing else. Everything is created. And
now I will show you what is happen. If
you switch to posted document, you will
see on the first side there is no
difference. This is one line with this
fixed assets. But what you need to do do
you need to go to find entries and when
you look into find entry in fixed assets
ledger entry you will have number 25. So
system automatically in the background
created 25 fixed assets. Just open this
entry and you will find all entries for
all of them. Everything is absolutely
the same as the first one. First one it
was fixed asset number 100 and then you
will have 110 120 130 using the same
number series you configure for fixed
assets. So everything is created here
and even if you switch to fixed assets
yes we will find all these fixed assets
already created into the system. So
that's it very easy. I think that with
this functionality automated a lot in
all these cases when you want to
purchase many of absolutely the same
items actually fixed assets.
So before we close this session I would
like to remind you to watch and to look
all these to use all these links to
depends what is about to watch some
videos to find interesting information.
This is really important. Remember all
of them. Subscribe on our Ling channel
so you can track our weekly news and all
announcements. And when you finish this
watching this video, remember there are
much much more other videos. So you can
use AKMSBC YouTube to find all videos
for this edition and from previous
editions and other videos as well. Thank
you for watching this session.